Guide to the Stanford University, Capital Planning and Management, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- NWC Alan Michelson project (Box 48, Folder 21)
- NWC Midrise Study (Box 48, Folder 22)
- NWC Organization (Box 48, Folder 23)
- NWC Orientation (Box 48, Folder 24)
- NWC Original Workplan (Box 48, Folder 25)
- NWC Outdoor Art (Box 48, Folder 26)
- NWC Overflow Space (Box 48, Folder 27)
- NWC Support (Box 48, Folder 28)
- NWC Surge Space, BCQ (Bio-Chem Quad) (Box 48, Folder 29)
- NWC Applied Physics (Box 48, Folder 30)
- NWC Electrical Engineering (Box 48, Folder 31)
- NWC Parking Survey (Box 48, Folder 32)
- NWC Phase II (Box 48, Folder 33)
- NWC Sequencing (Box 48, Folder 34)
- NWC Square Footage (Box 48, Folder 35)
- NWC Siting (Box 48, Folder 36)
- NWC Red Barn and Stables 1983 (Box 48, Folder 37)
- NWC SUFED (Box 48, Folder 38)
- NWC Summary of Protocols by Topic 1985 (Box 48, Folder 39)
- Facilities - 05-720 Governor's Corner (Box 48, Folder 40)
- Facilities - Quad 6 General (Box 48, Folder 41)
- Facilities - 06-010 Encina South (Box 48, Folder 42)
- Facilities - 06-010 Office of Development (Box 48, Folder 43)
- Facilities - 06-010 Economics (Box 48, Folder 44)
- Facilities - 06-020 Food Research Institute (Box 48, Folder 45)
- Facilities - 06-040 Encina Commons (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 06-050 Eating Clubs (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 06-100 Branner Hall (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 06-200 Toyon (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 06-300/350 Crothers (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 06-350 Law Student Center (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 06-400 Wilbur (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 06-500 Stern (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 06-600/650 Manzanita Park (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 06-910T/920T OOD (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 06-910T HandS Annex (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Facilities - Quad 7 General (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 07-310 Center for Molecular and Genetic Medicine (CMGM) (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 07-310 New Children's Hospital (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 07-310 Interim Chemical Storage (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 07-310 Research Animal Facility (RAF II) 1982 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 07-015 Schultz Auditorium (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 07-025 Parking Structure (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 07-050 Anatomy (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 07-080 DLAM (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 07-100 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Humanities and Sciences Space Planning 1986-88 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- DAPER Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation Plan 1987 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- DAPER Buck Estate Access and Parking 1982-83 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- NWC Green Earth Sciences Building 1991 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- NWC SU Square Feet Assignment 1991 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- NWC Bacchetti Presentation to AC 4/1984 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- NWC Interviews LLW (Box 50, Folder 4)
- NWC Presentations (Box 50, Folder 5)
- NWC Regional Planning (Box 50, Folder 6)
- NWC Status Reports (Box 50, Folder 7)
- NWC White Papers and Keynotes (Box 50, Folder 8)
- NWC Mid-rise Buildings (Box 50, Folder 9)
- NWC Keck (Box 50, Folder 10)
- NWC Regional Planning 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- NWC Campus Sign Plan 1987 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- NWC Foothills Plan 1987 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- NWC Regional Planning 1986 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- NWC Brochures and Fundraising (Box 50, Folder 15)
- NWC Classrooms (Box 50, Folder 16)
- NWC Bike Plan (Box 50, Folder 17)
- NWC Connectivity (Box 50, Folder 18)
- NWC Academic Program Info Notebook (Box 50, Folder 19)
- NWC Classrooms (Box 50, Folder 20)
- NWC A Long Range Model for Library Planning 1988 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Vegetation Management Plan Phase I 1983 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Study for Proposed Drama Department Theatre Complex 1988 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Role of Safety Analysis in Facilities Design at SU 1986 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- SSRL Development Plan 1987 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Feasibility Study - Geology Corner 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Feasibility Study - Peterson Lab 1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Feasibility Study - McCullough 1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Feasibility Study - Physics Tank 1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Feasibility Study - Varian Lab 1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Feasibility Study - Durand (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Cost Study - McCullough 1986 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Cost Study - Varian 1986 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Cost Study - Stauffer III 1986 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Seismic Risk Assessment of SU Buildings 1988 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Development of Stanford Museum (L. Eitner) 1964-1984 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- O and M Planned Maintenance Program 1982 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- NWC Plan Summary Planning Report 1987 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- NWC Plan Supplementary Planning Report 1987 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Connective Element Projects 1989 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- New Housing for Undergrad Students Manzanita Site Plan 1988 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- NWC Redevelopment Project Interim Report 1985 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- NWC Redevelopment Project Supplementary Report 1985 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Regional Planning SU Campus 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Landscape Design Guidelines 1989 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Transition Plan - Accessibility 3/1979 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Establishing Policy Guidelines for the Physically Limited March 1981 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- DAPER Plan and Summary 9/1987 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Procedure Guide for Interaction with University Architect 5/1991 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Campus Center Region Plan 5/1990 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- J. Henry Meyer Memorial Library Feasibility Study 1989 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Stanford University Land Use Policy 1971 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1977-1982 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1978-1983 (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast v.1and2 1979-1985 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1981-1984 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1982-1985 (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1983-1986 (Box 51, Folder 34)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1984-1987 (Box 51, Folder 35)
- Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast Summary 1984-1987 (Box 51, Folder 36)
- Land Use Plan and Supplement 1980 (Box 51, Folder 37)
- Stanford West (Box 51, Folder 38)
- Regional Plan - West Campus 12/1985 (Box 51, Folder 39)
- Master Plan for Exterior Lighting of SU 1979 (Box 51, Folder 40)
- Lake Lagunita Area Plan Report 1984 (Box 51, Folder 41)
- New Undergraduate Residences at Stanford 1979 (Box 51, Folder 42)
- Facility Project Development Process 1981 (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Oak Regeneration on SU Lands 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 44)
- Regional Plan - Near East, Frost, Serra 1989 (Box 51, Folder 45)
- Circulation Plan 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Main Quad Stone Restoration Study 1988 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Parking Plan 1991 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Medical Center Regional Planning Report 1988 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 07-100 Cantor Sculpture Garden (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 07-200 Old Chem (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 07-210 Mudd (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 07-206/207 Med Lab Renovations (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 07-220 Keck (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 07-220 Keck (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 07 Arts Center Complex Feasibility Study (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 02-510 Mechanical Engineering (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 02-520 Mechanical Engineering (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 02-530 Civil Engineering (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 02-540 Civil Engineering (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 02-550 Peterson Lab (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 02-560 Reprographic Services, MRI (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 02-570 High Temp Geo Dynamics Lab (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 02-580 Old Union Student Services Building (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 02-590 Nitery etc. (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 02-600 Clubhouse (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 02-610 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 02-620 Old Firehouse (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 02-630 SU Press Building (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 02-635 Bindery Building (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 02-Molniya Project (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 02-650 Storke Building (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 02-914 Delta Upsilon 553 Mayfield (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 02-915 Rogers House (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 02-916 Mariposa House (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 02-918 The Bridge (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 02-919 Bike Shop (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 02-920 Lathrop House (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 02-925 Columbae (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 02-926 Beta Theta Pi (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 02-930 Serra House Relocation (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 03-001 Stanford Art Gallery (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 03-010 Cummings Art Building (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 03-010 Snelson Sculpture (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 03-050 Career Planning (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 03-055 Clock Bell Tower (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 03-100 Hoover Tower (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 03-100 Hoover Tower Fire Safety (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 03-110 Lou Henry Hoover (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 03-120 Herbert Hoover Memorial Building (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 03-300 Green Library (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 03-200 Green Library - Tiered Stacks 1988 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 03-200 Green Library 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 03-210/200 Green Library Budget (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 03- Hoover Fountain (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 03-300 Education (General) (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 03-300 Cubberley Auditorium (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Facilities - 03-300 Education Dedication Ceremony 1983 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Facilities - 03-400 Meyer (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Facilities - 03-400 Disability Resource Center (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 03-420 Sweet Hall (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Facilities - Quad 4 General (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 04-10 Sequoia Hall (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 04-050 CIS (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 04-050 Ventura Hall Facility Survey (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Facilities - Planned Maintenance Program Books- CERAS, Stauffer, Encina, Forsyth, Memorial Hall, Pine, Margaret Jacks, Terman, Mudd, Ginzton, Varian, Herrin 1982 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Environmental Safety Facility Re-entrainment Study 1989 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Task Force on Personnel Policies and Administration 1982 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Staff Survey on Minority Issues and General Job Satisfaction 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Changing Nature of Undergraduate Attendance at SU 1974 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Study of the Stanford Faculty 1972 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Report of the Committee on the Professoriate at SU 1974 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Freshman Admissions and Financial Aid 1972-73 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Report of the Development Office Task Force on Centennial Fundraising 1983 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Stanford Fundraising in the 1980's 1982 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Insurance and Risk Management Report 1984 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Report: QSP Team on Work Simplifications 1987 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Survey on Health of Stanford Students 2/1987 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Plan for Future of Cowell Student Health Center 1986 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Report of the Faculty Practice Program - SU Medical Center 1987 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Undergraduate Admissions - Statistical Updates 1989 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Statistical Study of the Curriculum of 1987-88 AB/BS Recipients 11/ 1988 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Senior Survey 1989 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Final Report of the Annual Review 1990 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Reaffirmation of Accreditation 3/1981 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Accreditation Self Study 1991 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Compensation Proposal 1984-85 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Compensation Proposal 1985-86 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- BOT Committee on Investments Gift Real Estate Report (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Donald Kennedy Address "Stanford in 2010" 4/14/1988 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Humanities and Sciences Space Needs 1965-1975 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Bacchetti - Management Development Program Five Year Review (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Ambient Air Quality Study (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Western Culture Debate 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Building 10 Occupation 1989 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Art Museum (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Anderson Art Collection (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Kyoto Campus (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Child Care - West (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Major GPI Projects Forecast 1987 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Quad Restoration (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Tresidder Annual Report 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Tresidder Renovation Plan 1986 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Tresidder Feasibility Study 1987 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- BOT Working Group on Building Design and Siting (Box 56, Folder 25)
- BOT FandA Agendas 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- BOT Donald Kennedy "Pastoral" Letters (Box 56, Folder 27)
- BOT EDP Audits (Box 56, Folder 28)
- BOT Miscellaneous Committees (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Regional Planning Protocol (Box 56, Folder 30)
- Regional Planning - Senate Reports and Presentation 1987 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- General Use Permit Background 1988 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Design Review Group (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Architect Selection (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Philosophy of Architecture/Design Guidelines (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Archeological Resources Policy (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Facilities - Reserves Retrenchment 1982 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Facilities - Project Decision-Making (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Outdoor Art Budget and Management (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Outdoor Art Capital Budget Staff (Box 57, Folder 10)
- GPI Plan 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 07 Medical School Parking (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 07-520/520 Sherman Fairchild Bldg/Auditorium (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 07-530 Animal Research Facility II (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 07-530 CMGM (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 07-535T CMGM (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 07-550 Mayer Cancer (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 07-560 Medical Center Office Building (MSOB) (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 07-570 Magnetic Resonance Center (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 07-580 Medical School Lab Surge (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 07-920T Psychiatry Clinic Building (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 07-930T Primate Facility Annex (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 07-965T Central Aud - Mech Primate Facility (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 07-997T Chemical Waste Interim Facility (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Facilities - Quad 8 General (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 08-10 Encina Gym (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 08-100 Athletics/PE (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Facilities - 08-150 857 Serra (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Facilities - 08-160 855 Serra (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Facilities - 08-200 Old Pavilion (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Facilities - 08-320 Tanner Fountain (Box 57, Folder 31)
- Facilities - 08-350 GSB 1982-1987 (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Facilities - 08-360 GSB (Box 57, Folder 33)
- Facilities - 08-360 GSB 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 08-350 Pillars of Hercules Sculpture (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 08-350T Temporary Modular (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 08-360 Littlefield (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 08-400 Old Steam Plant (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 08-410 Galvez Storage Building (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 08-500 Galvez House (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 08-600 Frost Amphitheater (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 08-980T Peter Coutts Housing Trailer (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Facilities - Quad 9 General (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 09-105 Utilities Department Office Space (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 09-100 Bonair Gas Cylinder Storage (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 09-110 Bonair Stores (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 09-110 Bonair ID Mail (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 09-110 Bonair Logistics (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 09-120 Credit Union (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 09-140 Custodial Office (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 09-180 Canteen Warehouse (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 09-190 Telecommunications Center (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 09-200 Fire and Police Facility (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 09-250 Shell Service Station (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 09-300 Maples Pavilion (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 09-310 De Guerre (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 09- DAPER Field House Program Requirements (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 09-320 Cardinal Plaza (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 09-360 Sunken Diamond Press Box (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 09-370 Sunken Diamond Restrooms (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 09-375 Police Compound Stadium Trailer (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Facilities - 09-380 Varsity Tennis Court Restrooms (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Facilities - 09-385 Varsity Tennis Facility (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Facilities - 09-390 Private Residence Galvez/Campus Dr. (Trackhouse) (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Facilities - 09-400 Commissary (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Facilities - 09-500 Stadium (Box 58, Folder 32)
- Facilities - 09-001x Child Care at SU (Box 58, Folder 33)
- Facilities - 09-600 Storage, Equipment Athletics (Box 58, Folder 34)
- Facilities - 09-920T Little Kid's Place (Box 58, Folder 35)
- Facilities - Quad 10 General, Escondido Village General (Box 58, Folder 36)
- Facilities - 10-055 Escondido II (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 10-063 Highrise - Abrams (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 10-108 Rains (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 10-126 Escondido Highrise - Blackwelder (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 10-160 Escondido Cottage - Administration (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 10-170 Escondido Library (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 10-180 Escondido Community Center (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 10-300 Bing Nursery School (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 10-310 Tower House (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 10-320 Hacienda Apartments (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 10-610 Alpha Sigma 585 Cowell (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 10-700 Cowell Health Center (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 10-900T Escondido Village Maintenance Shop (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 11 Foothills Siting for Artists Studios (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 11 Row Houses General (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 11-105 Humanities Annex (Van Patton House) (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 11-110 Bolivar House (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 11-120 Hammarskjold House (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 11-130 Huston House (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 11-135 Dean of Chapel 659 Salvatierra Bicycle Path (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 11-190 Phi Sigma 564 Mayfield (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 11-644 San Juan Beta Chi House (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 11-180 Grove I (572 Mayfield) (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 11-200 Grove II (584 Mayfield) (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 11-220 Delta Kappa Epsilon 592 Mayfield (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 11-260 Durand (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 11-280 Roth House 713 Santa Ynez (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Facilities - 11-290 Theta Xi 717 Dolores (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Facilities Code - General, Related Problems (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Facilities Code - Hazardous Materials (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Facilities Code - Chemistry Flammable Storage (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Facilities Code - Biosafety Task Force (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Facilities Code - Asbestos (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Facilities Code - Deferred Maintenance (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Facilities Code - Elevators (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Facilities Code - Fire (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Facilities Code - Flammable Storage (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Facilities Code - Fume Hood (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Facilities Code - Fume Hood cont. (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Facilities Code - Hazardous Waste (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Facilities Code - OSHA (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Facilities Code - Earthquake/Seismic (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Facilities - Archaeological Review (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Facilities - Bike Safety (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Facilities - Childcare SNAP (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Facilities - Ethernet (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Facilities - Computer Science and Statistics Building (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Facilities - Conference Center Information (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Facilities - DCAA Facilities Audit (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Facilities - Debt Policy (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Facilities - Donor Recognition Project (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Facilities - Earthquake Action Group (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Facilities - Planning Guide Memo (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Facilities - Capital Budget Data Base (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Facilities - Database (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Facilities - Planning and Procedures - Process I, II (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Facilities - Plan and Funding Forecast (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Facilities - Meeting 1983 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Facilities and Planning Office 1978-1980 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Facilities and Planning Office 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Facilities and Planning Office Engineering Department (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Facilities and Planning Office External Staff Meetings (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Facilities and Planning Office Bill Massy Review (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Facilities and Planning Office Presentations (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Facilities and Planning Office Record (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Facilities and Planning Office Planning Principles Paper (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Facilities and Planning Office Protocol (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Facilities and Planning Office Small Projects (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Facilities and Planning Office Funding (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Facilities and Planning Office Student Report 1975 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Facilities and Planning Office Miscellaneous (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Facilities Office (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Facilities and Services (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Facilities Liaison Group (Box 61, Folder 15)
- GPI Policy and Procedure 1980-1989 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- GPI Cogeneration Project (Box 61, Folder 17)
- GPI Parking Structure (Box 61, Folder 18)
- GPI Telecommunications (Box 61, Folder 19)
- GPI Water Master Plan (Box 61, Folder 20)
- GPI Lomita Drive/Mayfield (Box 61, Folder 21)
- GPI Via Crespi (Box 61, Folder 22)
- GPI Water Study Map 1975 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- GPI 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Land and Facilities Meetings 1989 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Landscape Design Guidelines draft 1988 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Outdoor Art Panel (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Outdoor Art Policy (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Outdoor Art Noguchi (Box 61, Folder 29)
- Outdoor Art Rickey (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Outdoor Art Rodin (Box 61, Folder 31)
- Outdoor Art Roloff (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Outdoor Art Segal (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Outdoor Art Panel Serra St. (Box 61, Folder 34)
- Outdoor Art Stanford Family Statue (Box 61, Folder 35)
- Outdoor Art Syrkin (Box 61, Folder 36)
- Outdoor Art Turnbull (Box 61, Folder 37)
- Outdoor Art Zajac (Box 61, Folder 38)
- Sign System (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Sign System 1985-1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Space Off Campus (Box 62, Folder 3)
- West Campus Master Plan (Box 62, Folder 4)
- West Campus Working Group (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Housing - Housing for Single Graduate Students (HSGS) Project Group (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Housing - GSHP (Graduate Student Housing Project) Meeting Notes (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Housing - Jerry Parks (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Housing - Project Group (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Housing - Architect (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Housing - Process (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Housing - Schedule (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Housing - Architect Drawings (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Housing - Architect Selection (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Housing - Concept Site Approval (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Housing - Concept Approval (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Housing - BOT Write-up 10/1986 (Box 62, Folder 17)